This way.
Yeah, it's this way.
You and Daddy.
Papa.
What?
What? Who bought it?
Did you buy it?
A-ra?
Did Aiara buy it?
Yeah.
Yuzu bought one too?
Did you buy it, Tasaki?
What? No, I didn't.
For Mr. Tasaki.
Listen, listen.
The chair is downstairs.
Yes.
There it is.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
ah...
drunkard
Don't be
Always
What is it?
I'm so nervous
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, is it good?
This is Swister.
Hey, are you free later tonight?
Let's start with the applause.
What is it with you people? You come to all these places today and it's like...
Hey, are you free later tonight?
If you'd like, come with me.
I've always wanted to talk to Shunsuke Setoguchi.
Even after the rain, we're still having a chatting party!
Seino
It's raining, too
Ame-flash ame-rye!
Flip and flip
Ameshame
Combined with Yuzuki's Room
Janai Fo's Yuzuki's Room Special
To all of you who are watching the YouTube Live Ameflash Official Channel
Good evening everyone.
We are Ameshame Flash.
Please come on in.
So, you know, every single time.
Where we say 00 and...
With the hashtag Ameshabe.
from among those who tweeted us.
I choose a name from among those who have tweeted
I call out the names of those who tweeted about the event,
Today, I called Mr. Setoguchi, who has been advertising that there will be an Ame-shabu.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Setoguchi-san.
He wrote that he was going to appear on the program.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it.
And here comes the spacha.
Kazuman-san has sent us a Yuteki Hair Collaboration Memorial.
Thank you very much.
So, tonight's Ameshabe will be from a different place than usual.
We are broadcasting from the studio of Yuzuki Daikoku's show, Yuzuki's Room, on Team Shachi.
I never thought I would be able to do it here.
We are borrowing a part of the studio. We are very happy to be able to do this.
Thank you very much.
Oh, are you okay?
It's fine. It's really not that important.
Oh!
It's like, oh!
Oh, but it's like a breath of fresh air all by itself.
So it's not that important.
Well, please continue.
Once again, let me explain Yuzuki's Room,
This is a program that is distributed on Team Shirt's official YouTube channel every Monday night at 9:00 pm.
I would like to inform everyone about it.
I've been a guest on the show a few times now.
Yes, what's up?
I've been, I don't know, I've been hearing some voices, and I'm sorry, I've been hearing some voices, and I'm sorry.
The air conditioning was connected the whole time.
So if you can hear me backstage...
Is everything okay? Are you having a meeting or something?
No, I was backstage. I'm fine.
Okay, good, good. I see.
Yes, yes, yes, OK.
We were all guests.
Come on, let's all go a few more times.
I'm really glad.
Hey, you know. We also have a live TV show called Ameshabe every Monday night at 8:00 p.m., so we have Ameshabe until 9:00 p.m. and then we have a date night,
So, it's a regular schedule of Ameshabe until 9:00 pm, and then we have a date day,
I think that's the usual course of events.
So, it's a regular schedule.
That's right. But, you know, it should be a nice flow. It was supposed to be a good flow at this time of the day.
But, it was because of Hana Kojima, who is playing MC card at Ameshabe, and she is absent today due to her schedule,
Huh?
Because of Kojimahana's bad timing,
Yeah, I'm going to be pushed for about 20 minutes to finish.
I've been pushed back about 20 minutes.The reality is that we usually end up pushing it for about 20 minutes.
Is that so?
That's right.
We are always pushed.
That's right. The senior program.
We are both doing each other's work, but today you are going to appear in Yuzuki's room with me, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Even though I'm really pushing it, I'm going to show my dog video.
You are stubborn enough to make sure to complete your own corner without fail, aren't you?
That's right.
Today, the Agency was covering its own backside, and the person himself did not show up,
So God was watching.
That's right. God was watching.
I think God was watching.
He's covering his own backside. He saw us. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Yuuchan.
Thank you very much.
But you know, when Yusaki's room starts, the number of views on Ameshame always decreases.
Yes.
From Yusaki's point of view, there might be no damage.
That's right.
How did you come to be able to appear in Yusaki's room on such short notice?
Please send me a message, please send me a message.
- You are the oldest, right? You're not the oldest, are you?
- Oh, look at me.
You're the oldest, but you leave all that trouble to the younger ones?
- You want to talk a lot, don't you?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. If I have to explain everything to you later, you won't say anything about this candy-ass conversation.
- Explain.
- Go, go, go, go!
- What's with the older guy?
- Let me explain.
- Yuzuki and I collaborated on a song together.
- She collaborated on our AmeFlash song.
- We had a talk at the end.
- At that time, Yuzuki-chan said
- The room festival was great.
- Yuzuki-chan told us that the Room Fest was great, but that she would be happy if we could appear in Yuzuki's room on YouTube next time.
- We've been wanting to do it for a long time, too.
- We're going to do it soon.
- We said we would do it tomorrow.
- We said we would do it the day after tomorrow, and they said, "Well then, can't we do it the day after tomorrow? We were like, "Well, we can leave the day after tomorrow, right?
- More than lightly.
- Then the day after tomorrow.
- The staff didn't say anything to us either.
We haven't been told it's okay either.
Then we'll put it out the day after tomorrow.
We'll put it out the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow.
And we were given the OK!
It's amazing, isn't it?
I didn't think we'd be able to do it.
I'm really glad that you've been so patient with us.
We are so happy that you loved it and got on board.
Thank you very much.
So, that's the story.
Yes, that's right.
Well, we are a group with only one staff member.
I mean, even now, we welcome sudden offers.
That's right.
Momokuro-chan is also in the museum, Gege also stopped his crush, etc.
We are always here, you know.
Yes!
We are looking forward to your offer!
We are waiting for you!
No, we're not waiting for you.
This is the studio of Yusake's room.
I'm visiting my senpai's show.
I'm calling for offers from other shows.
What?
Absolutely not. It's rude.
You guys have "rude" written all over your faces.
You have rude faces! I can't push a rude-face idol!
Yeah, you two rude faces are the reason I'm done.
It's always you guys who screw things up.
You stupid idiots!
I gave you this.
But it says "cute" on your face, Mojikun.
It's pretty in pink letters.
Of course not. I'm looking at the camera and you're cute.
That's not true, but take a look.
It's true!
Then what? !
I really don't like it. Really?
Yuzuki's staff. I can hear them.
Someone's losing it. He's starting to lose it.
I'm on my senior's show, and here we go with the usual farce.
I'm scared to go on the show now.
It's like we're being evasive.
Wasn't it raining? It wasn't raining.
So there are people who want to do it like this. Yuzuki too.
Six hundred people are watching us.
Thank you so much, Yuzuki-chan!
Yuzuki-chan and Ms. Suzuguchi will be our guests tonight.
Yuzuki and Ms. Suzuguchi will be our guests tonight.
We don't know when they will appear.
Please don't miss the Yuzuki's Room that is not a new version of Amezaibari!
Please don't miss it!
I will read the spacha before the next step!
YTXFED Shippo's feelingsMr. YTXFED Tail Feelings
What?
Wait a minute.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm so thrilled to see Amershave and Yuzuki's room all the time.
Okay, listen.
Thank you very much.
The script says when to go over the top. It's a circle for emphasis.
You know, it says when to brace. It doesn't say when to brace.
You're supposed to cut me a break here. No, I'm not.
No, no, no. As expected of a second-generation actress, she's good at it.
I thought it was a credit card for boiler room training.
I was kind of hard on myself, too.
I'm glad to hear that.
Nao-san, congratulations on 300,000 views of Blow-Year-Mind!
Thank you!
It hasn't even been up for a month, but I'm really happy.
Naton-san, thanks for your hard work at the Yusuki hair festival rally!
Thank you very much.
We hope to talk a lot about the next episode on Hirabushi later this evening moon day, in the main story.
Please look forward to this one.
Thank you very much.
Now, shall we talk about yesterday's release?
Yes, I would like to talk about yesterday's release.
It was the first time for Ambue Flash.
But it's been a long time since we've had a laraport, Tatsuhiko Tachikawa, right?
Yes, it has.
I wonder how many years it has been.
But I saw a tweet from a fan,
It says it was in September 2017.
Five years ago?
I'd have to look.
Oh no.
So it's really around the end of 3WE, isn't it?
It's the first one, right?
Five years ago, so the last.
So we've been together for about 10 years now.
We did a lot of cover guests and stuff.
When you met 3WEJ, you moved out of your house, and you were working with the original group in a big group, right?
If it was a big group, then it was the 3WEJ.
And then you're in a smaller group, too, right?
And that smaller group is
Here.
They can dance to cover songs.
I mean, didn't that sound like something that would happen?
It was the day of the Music Station Ultrafest.
The music station was broadcasting live for hours from the morning.
So it was Sora and Harimo.
Oh, Moririn.
No, that's not right.
Moririn was probably some kind of irad.
Oh, that was Tetsuko Kuroyanagi.
That was another time.
Different time.
After that.
Then Solochan did the spring
He put on a katsuna and had candy planted in it.
That's right.
Tamosan's.
That was a long time ago.
I missed it so much when I first came.
The way he looked at us from upstairs.
That was a long time ago.
A long time ago.
But anyway, there were a lot more people than usual at the Reeve's.
I heard they had the largest crowd.
I heard people say, "We gave them more menstrual dogs than usual.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Some people didn't take the menstrual dogs and went outside to watch them.
Some people even went out of their way to watch them.
I mean, I'm sure there were a lot of people who came to see us on TikTok.
There were also many people who came to the event after seeing us on TikTok.
It made me really happy.
Yeah, it made me happy.
Yeah, I was happy.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The influence of TikTok.
I think you must have had the most relatives there.
Yes, this Tachikawa Tachibana Day.
There were a lot of relatives who lined up in line to get in line for the special event.
There were a lot of people standing in line for the benefit event.
There were a lot of people.
So it was like our usual benefit line was all relatives.
It was like all of us were relatives.
I, or rather, Ayura's relatives' line
It was twice as big as my usual benefit line.
What?
That was pretty amazing.
That's amazing.
There were so many of them.
So much so that I'm wondering if all these people
I was so surprised to see all these people.
We were all so surprised to see them.
Oh, it's so long! I thought, "Oh, my God, it's so long!
It's already turned around.
I was so surprised.
I can already see it in your eyes.
It was a lot, wasn't it?
Everyone was a lot, but of course...There were a lot of people, but of course
There were more of those.
If you put them all together, it would be more.
That's a lot, isn't it?
There were so many other members, too.
Yes, yes. I was so surprised.
I feel like I could run away with just your relatives already.
I was so surprised.
It was amazing.
I was very happy.
There is an atmosphere that the clientele is changing little by little.
What kind of atmosphere?
Up until now, it was the people who supported us who came to see us,
I had an image that there were a lot of people who had our goods on their bodies or somewhere,
I have an image that there were a lot of people who would come to our booth
I thought, "Let's drop in for a visit,
I don't know how to put it,
But now we have more people who just want to drop by casually,
There are people who seem to come here on their own time, and there are people who seem to be on their way home from club activities,
Some of them looked like they were just visiting for fun, others looked like they were on their way home from a club activity,
Some of them are just coming from club activities, and others are just here with their friends to see this girl,
Some of them were young, younger than us, junior high school students.
You can tell that the atmosphere is changing rapidly.
It's interesting.
It's amazing that the number of new fans who come to the show is not decreasing.
It's increasing.
That's right.
We keep releasing more and more.
I think that's amazing.
Usually, when you get a buzz once, you know it's going to get bigger.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think it was with this second person that we created a children's area, a family area, and so on.
Until now, there would never have been enough space for even one person.
It was never popular among children.
But now there are so many people in the family area.
Yes, it was cute.
It was so cute.
Everyone loves little kids.
Yeah.
Super cute.
So cute.
Mike, it's hard to hear you.
Is it coming back? I'll try to fix it.
It's not being typed. It's never been typed.
I guess it's okay now.
That's good.
I tried again.
But I can hear you.
I can totally hear you.
It's coming from your phone.
I can hear the little guy.
It's like it's coming from my phone.
I just fixed it a little bit now. What do you think?
I can hear it, though.
I can hear the members.
I can hear you.
It's not that I can't hear you.
What do you think?
I think I'll take a break.
I tried to breathe. I'm sorry. Always.
I'm sorry.
I really appreciate it.
My voice is okay.
Well, I'll try not to talk too much.
Okay.
But it's because we haven't done this in a while,
There were new people who came to see the show because they were curious about it,
But there were also those who always come to see us,
It's been a long time since we were there.
You mean since the time of 3B Jr.
And there were people who brought goods from 3B Jr,
Oh, really?
There were even people sleeping on the old, huge poster of flowers.
I remember that poster... I think there was a special offer where if you referred a friend, you got a huge poster of the paper.
That's right.
I remember it well.
I remember. The Apollo tour.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The one where the person who invited his friend to the Apollo tour at the Loppony Ektheater would get an extra-large poster of the paper.
That's what it was.
Right, so not everyone bought one or something.
So I've never seen anyone with their own poster.
Really?
You mean some of the people at the autograph car brought them?
No, I've seen them before.
Mana's seen them, I've seen them.
I have one of my own.
So maybe some of them don't have one.
Or because they're not here right now.
I have one, but they won't bring it to me.
You know, the person who invited my friend, because if it's not that grid, it's not in this world.
It's amazing that you have that.
It's a rarity, isn't it?
A lot of people brought embarrassing photos.
Like the privilege body.
It's a nostalgic place.
It's also a place where people can easily come.
I'd like to come back again.
The person who gave me the power was very kind.The power givers were kind.
The hospitality was amazing!
He even wrote us a fair strike.
and told us to come back again.
And he was waiting for us.
I'm so glad they were waiting for us.
We told them that we wanted to come back too.
There was a cafe across from the stage.
There was some kind of café across from the stage.
The guy who runs it bought us some sweets.
He bought us sweets, and he bought us sweets to split the two-minute score,
We had to play rock-paper-scissors for them,
It was really jam-packed.
It was a warm ranking site.
There are only a few days left for the release event,
There are many more events that I would like to announce here,
I would like to announce them here.
I'll start with the first one.
Which one do you want to start with?
Tomorrow?
Lilybeth first.
It's connected, isn't it?
The star-studded day of the rain forest releve has come to an end, and there are only two events left!
The first one is on June 11th at Aeon Mall 9, Aichi, Japan.
On the 11th, we will have a re-release at 12:00 pm on the 11th!
And the last re-release of the re-staging will be on June 24th at Raraport Toyosu!
The time has not been decided yet, but this is really the last coffee release.
We are aiming for a turnout of 500 people.
We are aiming to have 500 people at the event, so we are hoping to have 500 people at Raraport Toyosu.
I hope we can mobilize 500 people at Raraport Toyosu.
I would be very happy if you could invite a lot of your friends to join us.
Thank you very much.
We have been doing this since last year.
We've been doing it since last year.
Did you come yesterday?
Yes, I did.
You came?
It was a mystery.
What mystery?
I don't know.
It's just...
Of youth.
Why didn't he say anything?
And we've all made up our minds.
I didn't get it the first time.
Can you tell him I didn't see it?
Like you didn't understand.
I don't mean that in a soft way.
I'd like you to say that I didn't see the candy shovel.
I didn't see the candy shovel.
I didn't see it! I didn't see it.
I was skimming and skipping.
I didn't see it.
It's just that you said something really weird out of nowhere.
I knew it would happen.
Ai-chan's chan
Chan-chan of Chuchu-chan's memories
Chan-chan was decided...
What?
Poor Chan-chan!
Who told you that?
You don't get it the first time, do you?
Oh...
Like, "That's what he said.
I said that.
He said something like...
And then he said, "I love you, Meow!" and I said, "Meow!
I said "meow" and that was it.
But then, about 3 or 4 more people said something like...?
You don't understand? What's the right answer?
Someone told me... in the middle of the show.
He told me to talk.
It's a light cut, but it's not very bitter at all.
What do you think the answer was?
You have to say "kitty".
They were all cats? Five or six.
Five or six of them were all cats.
I said, what happened to the animals?
They said, "If you say 'I love you' and then your favorite animal, we'll put a bobi for that animal.
What the fuck is that? I love elephants. Hearn.
Elephants are good. Elephants are good.
What was that all about? It's really unexpected
I was really surprised, like everyone else who said weird stuff.
I thought you finally loved it. It's so cute.
He tried so hard to tell me.
But it was so long. Someone wrote it down and said it.
I had to say something.
And everyone's sense of rhythm is a little different.
That's true.
Moe-chan's cha-cha-cha!
The toy cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha.
They have no sense of rhythm at all.
It's cute.
It's a little mushy, isn't it?
So, what do you want to do this time, Koname?
Let's go with "aichi".
Hey.(Japanese) root
itchy
Just look at it.
I don't need four words like that.
What? I don't think about it, guys.
You sure?
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, yeah.
I bet there's someone who could say, "Let's make it harder.
Let's make it really hard.
Tettentenmuscle. Tettentenmuscle.
It's getting a little short.
to be continued
Tenten mus musmus, tenten shumus musmus
Ayumika, say it with me
Tenten bashibashi, tenten shmusumusu
Tentenemusmusmus, tendenemusmusmus
TENTEN DEN MUSHUMSSUU, OKAY!
You seem to be far away from the sound, so I'll give you a hand when I'm done.
Thanks.
I don't think so.
Say it again.
Okay.
Okay. - Okay.
What if I say it?
Say it?
You want to think about it for a minute?
Oh, you want to think about it first?
Yeah, I'll think about it.
You'll see it when I say it.
You want to say it later?
I don't know.
Hmmm...
What? Ten-ten musumuten?
I'm not going to tell you what Ten-Ten Musu Musuteng is, but...
Musu musu musu.
Tenten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
What do you guys want me to do?
Is there anything you want me to do?
Ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
Is there anything you guys want me to do?
I don't know, maybe I don't want to spend a lot of time here.
I don't know, maybe sing a song or dance a little bit in the past.
What? I've done that.
I've had a lot of fun singing.
You said people would sing?
Yeah, like the same song one more time.
Okay, I'll sing it.
What do you want me to sing? Not an American song.
Like the steps.
Let's do that.
We'll do it at the story time.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
If you're in the middle of a story time...
It's like, "Okay.
It has to be.
It's very limited.
You're welcome to sing.
Yes, please.
Okay, okay.
Yes, sir.
That was only the first one.
That's right.
Tomorrow, June 6th.
I'll be in the Watermelon Parlap.
Yes, sir.
For this benefit event, the emotion guessing game is back again, so...
ha-ha-ha.
It says "reprint".
It's back!
We will also have an emotion guessing game like the "Ha-da-da" game, and you can take as many still pictures as you want.
We will also have a game where you can take as many still pictures as you want. Please come and visit us.
And the public event, and the radio too.
I'm going to do a radio show called "Rain Storm, Rain Must Reduce! I'm doing a radio show called
That's coming up soon.
And it's only June...
It's June 5th.
And this is only until June 9th, and there are only a few more tickets left.
Don't forget to buy your tickets!
And June 11th.
Uh, Lala... uh, Toyo... uh, Toyo...
tokonabe
I don't want to push it here.
I'm going to have a release event at Tokonabe.
After the release event.
I've been asked to perform at the Listfest 2pieces 23.
Yes, this way, you know, various things...
We will be performing at our home event on the 11th, so please come and join us!
Please come and visit us!
It's one of the biggest circuit festivals in Nagoya. Please come and play!
Please come!
I will be performing at a solo event called "Acoustic Night Fantasy" on July 4.
It's an acoustic event, so I'll be performing as an accordionist.
There will also be other idols, including Minnie.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous, but it will be really reassuring to have everyone there,
I'm thinking of including songs I've never played before in the set list,
I always think of everything by myself.
So I hope you are looking forward to it.So I hope you are looking forward to it.
The tickets are available from June 3 to July 3,
They are already on sale, so we are waiting for you.
Next!
On July 15, we will be performing at Spark 2023 in Yamanaka, Japan.
We will be accepting second round selections from Thursday, June 1st at 8pm until Thursday, June 2nd at 11:59pm.
When does it start today? There is still time.
Please get to your rooms as soon as possible, in case some of you forget to do so.
And next!
We will be at a Taiwanese festival called "Manga Expo" from July 27th to July 31st,
We are going to the Taiwanese festival called "Manga Expo" from July 27th to July 31st.
Taiwan!
Taiwan Satellite. Hey everybody!
This is Taiwan Satellite.
This is kind of cute.
I don't know what kind of festival it is.
I'm going to be designated for this, so I hope we can all work together to make it a production again.
Please do.
That's emo. We can broilermind in Taiwan.
And finally, we, Amehera City, will have our one-man live, Biosai 2023, on July 9 at Shinjuku Renee.
And what a surprise, we decided to make this one part soul down.
I'm so glad.
Thank you very much. Ladies and gentlemen, the first part is the soul down.
It was a month ago.
There is no such regression, we.
Yay.
But, you know, the second part, it means we have a little bit more left.
Really close.
So I just read on Twitter that people were going to go to the first part and were disappointed because they didn't have tickets.
Why didn't you come for the second part?
There were many more.
I hope you all don't have that regret again.
First things first.
I don't know, I'm looking at 177 people. I think some of you are new to this.
I don't know. I hope you will come and see us before you regret that you couldn't take pictures. I hope you will come and see us before you regret not having taken any pictures.
Thank you very much.
Spacha will do it.
Yes, I'm Spacha.
Mr. Kofi told me that he has been listening to the song while preparing in the morning to get excited. He said, "Please do your best from now on.
Thank you very much.
So, I'm sorry to say that 28 minutes have already passed from here.
It's so bad!
Why is there such a large group of people here?
Such a group of people.
Okay, so this is Tokyo Evificent Setoguchi-san.
Please come on in.
Thank you.
We will close the communication tomorrow.
May I?
What would you like to talk about?
This way, please.
Thank you very much.
Yes, please.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
When it comes to here, it's a personal card from Stacomi.
Oh, good for you. Finally, the candlelight tickets have arrived, Staatskommissar.
I'm sure we didn't lend you any more on the train, did we?
Indeed. Can we turn this way a little more?
Everyone can proceed a little more.
Back?
Is this okay?
It's okay, right?
Thank you so much for today.
Congratulations.
Is it okay if I take a bath?
Yes, please.
So, from now on, it's Yuzuki's room, not Yuzuki's room!
Please take care of her!
Please!
Good evening, everyone! My name is Yuko Okurayanagi.
All of Okurayanagi and Okurayanagi and Yuko, it's a hard to understand project.
This is a corner, right?
In this corner, Yuko Okurayanagi will ask our guests Moeka Aira and Yanagi-chan Setoguchi questions in a reckless manner,
The four of them will answer the questions without NG.
Of course, of course!
This is the most disgusting corner.
No NG?
No, nothing.
Okura-san, you have a lot of NG.
You do?
Not at all.
It's just like something in my eyes.
Also, he drinks uncle's drink.
I have to drink it and play "beg me.
Oh, I see.
If you buy me something during the concert, I drink uncle's drink.
It's uncle glue, in various ways.
It was uncle nori.
It's an exhibit.
Oh, I see.
Then I have a question for Yuko Okurayanagi from here.
I can't do that.
Well, I can't.
Is the NG too big? Yes.
Yes, I have nothing but NG.
I see.
Yes. So, I am going to ask you questions.
Yes. Let's get started. Tonight's guests are Mr. Lamehera from the topical group, and Yuko Okurayanagi and Mr. Fukugaku from the team presidents. Please give them my best regards.Yes, I am. Let's begin. Tonight's guests are Mr. Lamehera from the group of the topic, and Yuko Okurayanagi and Mr. Fukugaku from the team presidents. Please give them my best regards.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I was groaning. I'm in.
Please give my best regards.
Are you normal Yasuko-san, sexy Yasuko-san, cute Yasuko-san, or cool Yasuko-san?
Yes!
All of them are together.
All of them were together.
All of them, all of them. Not even the word "sexy".
Which one is your sexy Yasuko-san?
Today's sexy is Yasuko-san here.
Yasuko-san here.
Why is she different?
She changes her style on the day.
Koiin.
Chic.
Classy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for doing this.
You can keep on throwing things in there like this.
Yay!
That means I can make a move on you, too.
Can I do it now?
No, I'll use my New Year's money.
Who are you talking to?
Such a weak boy.
Who are you talking to? I'm scared.
I'm scared.
They're scared.
She's scared.
Even at school, Yuko always seems to be the lowest in rank.
That's not true.
Hurry up!
Oh, go ahead.
What is it like that?
Before this, it's bad.
It's bad.
What was that crap about you snapping?
I saw it!
You were watching?
What's with that sniping?
I've been under a lot of stress lately.
I've been snapping at the script all the time.
It's like he's in a frenzy. Does he do that every time?
He's been snapping at me a little lately.
Oh, I see.
What for?
What are you practicing for?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting for the application form moderator.
Please do.
Yes, keep me waiting.
Are you sure they're all right?
I'm scared.
What's going to happen?
Let's start with a few things,
First of all, I'd like to talk to Daikoku-san, who I'm sure you've all been waiting for.
I'm scared.
Mr. Daikoku, I was thinking about you when I saw your outfit today.
Actually,
I thought it would have been better if you hadn't worn the purple color.
I see.
I wanted to be a different color.
You wore pink today, didn't you?
Yes, it was. I think so, don't you?
I like Reiri Takagi,
I like purple,
I thought purple was good only for that reason,
If Rei-chan had a different color,
I would have preferred pink.
Really? Is that so?
But I wanted Rei-chan's color to be the same as the color of my hips,
I was happy with purple after all,
But if I had taken it off, I would have worn it in pink,
The color I wore was pink.
Wow.
So, if you had made a pink costume for a character or something, they would have changed it.
It might have been, right?
Hey, I'm not a member.
Well, I'm not a member.
Ha-ha-ha.
A little bit,
I don't know what you mean by "a little bit.
Oh, I see.
I like the color pink, and your costumes are pretty pink, too, aren't they?
I wanted to wear pink.
I wanted to wear pink, but now I'm wearing purple.
I have no complaints now.
No complaints.
Oh, I see.
I see. You know, the color you like, the color you want to do.
There are, aren't there?
Yes, there are.Yes, there is.
Oh, Petrasi, you don't have color?
Yes, in case you were wondering.
You say that unofficially?
What color is it?
Purple.
Oh, purple?
But it's the other color, yellow.
I'll match it with the new outfit.
Oh, no.
No, I like purple. It's purple.
Ah.
My favorite color, then.
Um, it's unofficial, so I could have said anything.
Oh, I see.
It's not okay to say it, is it?
I see.
What color are you?
Well, I'm red,
But my favorite color is black.
Ah.
Black.
So you like black.
It's hard to see.
It's hard to see,
Second.
I like red.
Yes, I like red.
You like strong colors.
Yes, I do. White and simple colors.
I see.
I bet you really liked the black and red outfit, didn't you?
It was great.
I saw it.
It was cool.
It looked good on you.
I'm yellow.
Oh, yellow. I know.
It's like a "Genki" sign.
I'm sorry, but aren't you the most energetic?
Ha-ha-ha.
You've got it all over you, don't you?
It's another type of yellow.
But we all decided on this color by ourselves.
Hmmm...
I decided to go with purple, Aira decided to go with red, and Hana decided to go with blue,
I want purple, Aira wants red, and Hana wants blue.
green, yellow, white, red, or pink.
Oh, so many.
That's why there are a lot of fans.
Before the goods were released, they would wave the colors we mentioned.
they wave the color we said.
Oh, yes, yes.
I've said so many things that it's all very disjointed.
Ha-ha-ha.
More colors than the number of people.
We didn't like that either,
We didn't like it,
I don't like it.
Why so many colors?
We wanted to dye it in different colors.
So we thought, "You should dye it yellow.
But yellow suits me.
There are so many.
I understand.
So we are quite satisfied with it.
We are convinced.
I am jet-black.
I envy you.
Oh, that's right.
I don't know about you, but black is great.
But, you know, jet-black in color.
Dark color.
I really like the dark color.
That's a very chuunibi way of putting it.
It's full of it.
So many.
You said that earlier.
I'm sorry.
That's outrageous.
What is it?
We're fine to meet, too.
It's hinged.
Quite a bit.
I think we have a good relationship.
No, but you don't follow me on Twitter.
Ha-ha-ha!
I don't know!
Only idols know about that.
But I am an idol, though.
Shippo-Blue.
What kind of commercial is "Shikkou-Blue"? What kind of commercial?
What kind of commercial?
I want to know!
I don't know, but I was surprised to find out that Yuzuki has appeared many times in Yuzuki's Room, which we are going to do later on.
You've been on the show quite often.
Yes, of course, it has something to do with that.
What is it?What is it?
Can't we start making a guess like Yuzuki-chan did for Ameheraci?
Oh, a guess?
I think there actually are.
I think it's changing the way we look at each one of them.
Then I want them to appeal to me.
That's extravagant!
Ha-ha-ha!
That's not funny!
If you want people to decide, you should appeal to them.
It's the heart of the guest.
Funny, funny!
I'll let you decide.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can I decide? It's a positive.
Can I decide? Positive.
Oh, Fukkyo-san said she recommends Moeka-san.
That's right.
I wonder why.
She might do her own face.
Oh, is that what you mean?
Surprisingly, the chat section is properly rough, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha!
In case you're wondering, it says "Don't forgive.
Don't forgive me, don't forgive me!
I wonder what I should do.
It's better to be honest about this, even if it's just from an Amefura-chan point of view.
But do you want me to push? For me.
I'm all about one person.
One person is important.
Well, I'll be honest with you.
You're here.
I've never heard of you before.
It's me, Mayaka.
Yay! Thank you very much.
I don't like it when someone says that.
I knew you liked it this way.
Hey.
You realize you're popular, right?
I think I'm popular.
After listening to "Moyaka" just now,
I got sick of you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
First of all.
First of all, in the comments section, I was like, "I recommend you, Moyaka-san.
I was about to say, "Well, I'm going to recommend Mayaka-san.
I thought he was going to say it with a microphone.
I was told.
It was the original one, wasn't it?
If it's different, I can't properly say why it's Oshi.
I can't say.
I can't say, "It's not because everyone told me it's different.
It's because, you know, look at it, it's fleeting.
Oh, it's fleeting. Very fragile.
It's like, you know, you have a nice sadness.
It's gentle and kind.
I don't know if this sounds like a comedian's comment, but..,
But that's the kind of skill that Amehura has.
Indeed.
I thought it was interesting.
The fragility in the strong is a beautiful feeling.
It's like your voice doesn't reach them.
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't know about that.
It doesn't reach me.
I think it's nice.
By the way, I really don't know anything about you.
It's not nice to meet you,
Nice to meet you.
As a face fan.
Isn't that the last thing you want?
The Minister's Award?
You don't like that? Not a bit.
It's like when you first meet someone, you instinctively know who you like.
I want the Minister's Award.
I want it in a good way.
But maybe that too.
Eh? I'm glad. I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
Well, I guess we all tend to do that now.
This is the first time I've heard of Stabla's guesses, and I haven't heard many.
I'm glad.
I'll say it again today without NG.
I like it.
But I was surprised by the gap, Ira.
Why? I understand.
Before I met you, I thought you seemed really cool.
I thought so too.
I get that a lot.
Right? That's what I thought.
I'm Ira, 20 years old.
I don't really make eye contact with people, but I'm kind of like that,
But I'm glad to know that she talks a lot.
You came to the Yusuki no Yarubesu, right?
When our eyes met, he waved to me, which made me very happy.
Gap, such a wonderful thing.
You didn't have a hard-on? Yes, I did. I had a little bit of a crush on him.
I'm sorry. Stop waving.
It's okay. It's okay. That's enough.That's enough. That's enough.
I have to do it for fanservice now.
You can't stop.
Just a little bit.
What, like that?
Like that.
And the neck.
Yes.
I wonder.
But you know what I mean.
You understand, don't you?
I do. I totally get it.
I like you just the way you are, too.
Are you trying to make a gap?
Are you aiming for a gap?
It was quite a gap.
I was in the first grade of junior high school when I first met Daichi,
I was dancing in the back of Power Go at a festival,
I thought he had a great dancing style that I really liked,
I was paying attention to him.
I'm really happy.
I like her because I have an image of a cool girl who is a good dancer.
So I thought she was really cool,
She's really easy to talk to.
I'm so happy.
For a lady?
Of course.
I have a gap one-sided love.
It's like a gap key.
Another one-sided love?
No, I like you a lot.
I was rejected by the material.
No, I didn't.
I'd like to know how you were rejected.
Let's see, when I said I love you, Mr. Daichi,
I'm sorry, I'm not you.
I didn't say that.
You started with number one, didn't you?
You didn't say that.
Yuzu, you didn't, did you?
I'm not you.
I didn't say it.
You're all wrong.
Really?
I love you.
I'm not turned on by you.
I didn't say that.
Then you should hug me, Mei.
Bang, bang, bang.
That's terrible.
Yes, it is.
I love it.
I'm glad to hear it with Elonie.
Thank you.
Please tell me you really love me all the time.
I really love you.
You say it all the time.
Even during the delivery.
You say it.
It's so cool.
I'm glad.
Okay, one more question.
Yes, please do.
Even louder,
Shall I say two?
Yes, please.
Your guess was Mr. Suzuki, right?
Yes, that's right.
Your guess is Kojima-san, right?
Yes, I do.
At least one person is there.
No way. He's not here.
Yes, yes. It can't be helped.
It can't be helped.
So, as for Ameherach..,
What number shall we put on the list?
Ah.
Here we go.
It's real.
What genre is this?
What is it?
You like it?
Yes, I do.
I like this genre.
Wow.
Oh, well.
Well, well, well... I'm not here to try hard to get back into it. I'm not making any mistakes.
I often get questions like that, even though there will be more distribution after this.
No, that's why the power of the delivery after this will not change. No power?
No power? No, no power.
Because the MC is already ranking them. You say no MCs, right?
That's right. Yes, I do have a power. No, but I like it a lot. I really like it.
I want it so bad. No, no, no, no. I can tell you right now.
Are you sure? I'm sure. I can tell you, but what are you going to do now, Mr. Omura?
I'm really confused. I don't know what to do. Do you like him?
I like him. I guess. Can I have all the groups?Likes. I think I like it. All groups okay?
All groups are fine. All the groups in the staff run. Yes.
Yes!
Ah!
Aah!
Here I go!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
How many stabla groups are there? How many do we have?
Ten...
There's a lot of us!
Twelve together...
Five, six, ten, yes, eight,
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Nine,
Oh, 10, 10, 10, 10, group of 10.
Ten groups, like, 10 like, 10 like.
What if I'm wrong?
It's 10.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't wait to get this over with, somehow.
The general honeymaster will put in this solo and stuff.
Oh, grand, honeymaster.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I'm okay with a group this time.
If it ends up here, it'll be an oshimeji
Uh, yeah, right.
Okay, then. Ten.
Woo, here we go.
Here we go.
Okay.
I'll be honest with you.
Seino
First place.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
You're number one.
I'm doing it.
No, I'm doing it.
Kind of.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm trying to get people to like me.
I'm doing that.
No, I don't feel good right now.
What about you?
What do you think, guys?
I want to make it to the top 10.
Oh, come on, Moeka.
Don't make me say that.
What?
I'd like to know the real number 10.
It's not a hello.
Wait a minute, I was wondering about #4, too.
Fourth place is high.
No, much higher.
Real fast.
Very high.
By the way, I don't hear all of them.
You can't hear the one before us.
Just the one before us.
So we're in third place?
Yes, that's right.
It's real.
Text me here and write it down.
I can't hear you over here.
That's aggressive. Really.
I can't hear you just here.
Before here.
I think it's Kimisa again.
Kimi-sa.
Yeah, really.
There's a slight difference.
This is Basho.
Wow! I knew it. I knew it.
Bathtub localism. There's a bond.
This one in first place.
Wow.
This one in Firefly.
No, it is.
But thank you.
It's my mistake. I should put this kind of pretense in there.
There you go.
Do you have a song by Megura?
Yes, I do.
Do you have it?
That's the one.
I really want to go to the one-man show.
I really want to go.
I really do.
So, that proves that you really like them, right?
Yes.
I'm just talking about my desire to go, so I guess that doesn't prove anything, does it?
I wanted to go this far.
Yes.
Maybe we're on the same page.
Ichikata-san.
You're teaching me this one-man show right now, right?
I'm wearing Mr. Omiya's sweater.
Yes, I am.
Gorigorously.Gory.
Yes, sir.
What are you going to do?
Are you going now? This is it.
I want to go.
Mr. Omiya, you are wearing an absent sweater.
I wore it at the hair festival,
I'm also wearing a variegated sweater with Yuhiki-chan,
I'm wearing a shirt while saying that I have another 8 days tomorrow.
No, no, it can't be helped that I'm wearing a shirt.
It can't be helped.
We are a work group.
But the times are different.
But, Mr. Omiya, you said you were involved in other things,
No, let's go to Tachikawa.
Then I thought I could go to Tachikawa,
Shibuya.
Well, I thought we could go to Tachikawa, and then Shibuya. I thought so, too.
Timing-wise, we can go there.
We really need you to take a break, so please don't come.
Please leave.
I want to go.
I'm a little sorry,
You just heard Mr. Omiya's confession, right?
Yes, I did.
What about the team shirt?
No, wait. He's running away. Say it first.
Yeah, I'm running.
Why are you being so stupid?
Laugh it up.
You're a genius, aren't you?
Well, I've never ranked anything before,
So you're saying I'm ranked number one because I just did it for the first time?